Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Student records and grades, 1970-2007; Accession 2016-A-046
  - GSAS Grades, 2004-2005, Accounting-History of Art
    - Experimental Pathology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Experimental Pathology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Film Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Film Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - French Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - French Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Genetics Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Genetics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Geology Geophysics Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - Geology Geophysics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - Germanic Languages Literature Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Germanic Languages Literature Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - History Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - History Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - History of Art Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - History of Art Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - GSAS Grades, 2004-2005, History of Science Medicine - end
    - History of Medicine Science Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - History of Medicine Science Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Immunobiology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Immunobiology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - International Relations Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - International Relations Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Investigative Medicine Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Investigative Medicine Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Italian Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Italian Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Linguistics Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Linguistics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Management Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Management Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Mathematics Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Mathematics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Microbiology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Microbiology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochem Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochem Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Molecular, Cell Development Biol. Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Molecular, Cell Development Biol. Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Masters Thesis Research Spring 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Music Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Music Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Neurobiology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Neurobiology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Neuroscience Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Neuroscience Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Pharmacology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Pharmacology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Philosophy Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Philosophy Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Physics Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Physics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Political Science Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Political Science Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Psychology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Psychology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Religious Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Religious Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Russian, East European Hellenic Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Russian, East European Hellenic Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Sociology Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Sociology Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Spanish Portugese Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Spanish Portugese Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Statistics Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Statistics Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - South Asian Studies Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - South Asian Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Teacher Prep. Fall 2004 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Theater Studies Grades Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Law School Grades Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Law School Spring Grades 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Visiting Assistant in Research Fall 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Visiting Assistant in Research Spring 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Womens, Gender, Sexuality Studies Spring 2005 Grades, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - No Mark (NM) Spring 2005, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - GSAS Grades, 2005-2006
    - Undergraduate Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - African Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - African Studies Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - African-American Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - African-American Studies Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - American Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - American Studies Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Anthropology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Anthropology Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Archaeology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Architecture Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Art Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Astronomy Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Astronomy Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Cell Biology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Chemistry Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Chemistry Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Classics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Classics Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Comparative Literature Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Comparative Literature Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Computational Bio and Bioinfo Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Computer Science Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Computer Science Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Drama School Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - East Asian Languages Lit Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - East Asian Languages Lit Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Economics Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - Economics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Engineering Applied Science Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Engineering Applied Science Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - English Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - English Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - European Russian Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Film Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Film Studies Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - Forestry Environmental Studies Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - French Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - French Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Genetics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - Geology Geophysics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Geology Geophysics Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Germanic Languages Literature Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - Germanic Languages Literature Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 112)
    - Greek Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 113)
    - History Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 114)
    - History Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 115)
    - History of Art Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 116)
    - History of Art Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 117)
    - History of Medicine Science Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 118)
    - Immunobiology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 119)
    - Immunobiology Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 120)
    - International Relations Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 121)
    - International Relations Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 122)
    - Italian Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 123)
    - Italian Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 124)
    - Law School Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 125)
    - Law School Spring Grades 2006, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 126)
    - Linguistics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 127)
    - Linguistics Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 128)
    - Management Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 129)
    - Management Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 130)
    - Mathematics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 131)
    - Mathematics Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 132)
    - Medieval/Renaissance Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 133)
    - Medieval/Renaissance Studies Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 134)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochem Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    - Molecular, Cell Developmental Biol. Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 137)
    - Molecular, Cell Developmental Biol. Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    - Music Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 139)
    - Music Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 141)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    - Neuroscience Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    - School of Nursing Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 144)
    - Philosophy Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 145)
    - Philosophy Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 146)
    - Physics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 147)
    - Physics Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 148)
    - Politicial Science Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 149)
    - Political Science Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 150)
    - Psychology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 151)
    - Psychology Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 152)
    - Religious Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 153)
    - Religious Studies Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 154)
    - Russian, East European Hellenic Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 155)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 156)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 157)
    - Sociology Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 158)
    - Sociology Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - Spanish Portuguese Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 160)
    - Statistics Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - Statistics Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 162)
    - Southeast Asian Studies Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 163)
    - Visiting Assistant in Research Fall 2005 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 164)
    - Visiting Assistant in Research Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 165)
    - Women and Gender (WGSS) Spring 2006 Grades, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 166)
  - GSAS Grades, 2006-2007
    - African Studies Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - African Studies Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - African Studies Fall 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - American Studies Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - American Studies Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Anthropology Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Archaeology Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Astronomy Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Astronomy Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Cell Biology Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Cell Biology Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Chemistry Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Classics Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Classics Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Comparative Literature Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Comparative Literature Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Computer Science Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - East Asian Languages Lit Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Economics Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Economics Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Engineering Applied Science Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Engineering Applied Science Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - English Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - English Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Epidemiology Public Health Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Film Studies Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Film Studies Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - European and Russian Studies Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Forestry Enivronmental Studies Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Forestry Enivronmental Studies Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - French Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - French Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Genetics Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Geology Geophysics Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Germanic Languages Literature Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - History Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - History Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - History of Art Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - History of Art Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - History of Medicine Science Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - History of Medicine Science Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Immunobiology Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - International Relations Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - International Relations Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Investigative Medicine Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Investigative Medicine Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Italian Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Italian Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Law Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Law Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Linguistics Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Linguistics Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Management Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Management Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Mathematics Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - MD/PhD Program Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Medieval/Renaissance Studies Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Medieval/Renaissance Studies Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochem Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Molecular Cell Developmental Biology Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Molecular Cell Developmental Biology Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Music Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Music Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilization Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Neuroscience Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Nursing Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Nursing Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Pharmacology Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Pharmacology Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Philosophy Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Philosophy Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Physics Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Political Science Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Political Science Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Psychology Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Religious Studies Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Religious Studies Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Slavic Languages Lit Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Sociology Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Sociology Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Spanish Portuguese Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Spanish Portuguese Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Statistics Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Visiting Assistant in Research Grades Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Visiting Assistant in Research Grades Spring 2007 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Women+Gender Studies Fall 2006 Grades, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Teacher Prep Grades Summer 2006 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Statistics-Pfizer program student records (program discontinued in 2002)
  - Exchange Scholar Student Records
    - Exchange Students, 1970's (Box 18, Folder 125)
    - Course Exchange, Princeton University, 1970's (Box 18, Folder 126)
    - Exchange Scholars, Yale Students, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 127)
    - Exchange Scholars, Visitors, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 128)
    - Exchange Students, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 129)
    - Exchange Scholars, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 130)
    - Exchange Scholars, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 131)
    - Exchange Scholars, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 132)
    - Exchange Scholars, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 133)
    - Exchange Scholars, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 134)
- Grade rosters and student records, 1920-2003; Bulk 1990-2003; Accession 2016-A-065
  Restricted until January 1, 2079.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (GSAS) Grade Rosters
    - African American Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - African Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
    - American Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    - Anthropology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Archaeology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - Astronomy, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - Biology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
    - Cell Biology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
    - Chemistry, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    - Classics, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - Comparative Literature, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
    - Computer Science, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
    - East Asian Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
    - Economics, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
    - English, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 34-35)
    - Experimental Pathology, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 36-37)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
    - French, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
    - Genetics, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 42-43)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 44-45)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
    - History, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 48-49)
    - History of Art, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 50-51)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 52-53)
    - International Relations, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 54-55)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 56-57)
    - Linguistics, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 58-59)
    - Mathematics, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 60-61)
    - Medieval Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 62-63)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 64-65)
    - Music, Dept of, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 66-67)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 68-69)
    - Neurobiology, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Operations Research/Management Science, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
    - Organizational Behavior, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
    - Pharmacology, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
    - Philosophy, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
    - Physics, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Political Science, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
    - Psychology, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
    - Religious Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
    - Sociology, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 24-25)